This week, you may have been surprised to find out about a brand new terror cell that's apparently carried out about a half dozen bombings across Europe, mainly targeting Jewish-linked sites in Belgium and the Netherlands.
It's being called Ashab al-Yamin, and it took Israeli intelligence firm less than six hours to determine that, surprise, Iran did it.
But it turns out there are some pretty glaring questions remaining.
Questions like, why hasn't anyone been killed or injured in any of the explosions?
Why are they targeting Belgium and the Netherlands instead of countries like France that are actually directly involved in the war?
And why have so many suspects been released on bail?
Why do they keep referring to Israel in their messages instead of saying occupied Palestine or Zionist regime or any of the other ways Islamic resistance groups usually avoid that term?
In other words, why do they seem to communicate like Israelis?
Now, mainstream media and these Israeli-led groups feeding them information claim that Ashab al-Yamin has all the hallmarks of an Iranian proxy group.
But in reality, it has all the hallmarks of an Israeli false flag.
This is something that Israel's intelligence has done since it was created in 1948.
In the early 1950s, a series of explosions targeting Jews in Iraq were mostly minor, with only one causing fatalities, but they convinced around 95% of the Jewish population, over 100,000 people, to move to Israel.
Decades later, Yakov Karkuli, a member of the Zionist underground there, admitted that Israeli intelligence was responsible.
And he said the objective was, quote, to terrorize and not to kill, so local Jews would feel forced to leave.
A whistleblower at MI5, Annie Mashon, said something similar happened in 1994 when Israel's embassy in London was hit with a car bomb and around 20 people were injured, mostly not seriously.
Mashon later said that a senior British intelligence agent in charge of that case determined that Mossad had bombed their own embassy in order to pressure officials in London for more protection and to frame Palestinian organizers who weren't even anywhere near the scene.
Two innocent Palestinians were arrested, charged, and convicted of conspiracy to cause that attack.
They were very active in a Palestinian support network in London, and they were getting some traction in the media.
They were getting quite a lot of support.
So by arresting these people and framing them from the attack and sticking them in prison, the whole network just shattered and hasn't got back on its feet to this day.
So what's happening now?
Well, we have a series of bombings that isn't causing much physical harm beyond property damage,
and it's clearly not convincing governments to be friendlier to Iran.
What it is doing, however, is helping trigger a public panic in the West over secret radical Muslims supposedly attacking us for Iran,
while also creating the feeling among Jews that they're not safe in the diaspora and that they'd be better off in Israel.
Frankly, I don't see how any of that benefits Iran, but you wouldn't have to look too far to see who it does.